Gajesingh Bhati () Featured

MCA with 3.4 years of experience in java full stack developer with angular.

Expertise in java, spring, angular, sql, javascript.

Good leadership skills and Logical skills.



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Current Company: TalentServ Consulting Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Current Location: Pune
Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: html,javascript,sql,core java,hadoop,advance java,ajax,json,spring,maven,angularjs,hibernate,spring

mvc,spring boot,mockito,junit,Java 8,Nodejs

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

My name is Gajesingh Bhati. I have completed my MCA(computer science) in 2017 with 1st class from pune University .I am currently working as a java full stack developer(angular,java,sql ,mongodb,javascript, typescript, spring boot) with 3.4 years of experience. I have completed the internship in BigData Hadoop from Clairvoyant Biz. Pvt ltd. I always love to learn new technology.I am adaptable in nature.my grasping power and analytical skills are excellent.Currently

Work Experience

TalentServ Consulting as Software Engineer

Jan 2017 to Till Date

Working as a java full stack developer (Java Angular, javascript, spring)

as Pune

Jan 2016 to Jun 2016

I have completed the internship from clairvoyant bizinfo pvt.ltd.l worked as a software developer,web page designer.we used the different technology like Html,Css,Css3,Java,Jsp,BigData Hadoop.The project was on BigData Hadoop.

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Pune University in 2014

PG: MCA (Computers) from Pune University in 2017

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Java

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
SQL	Oracle 11g	2019	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
JAVA		2019	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
HTML,CSS		2019	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Big-Data Hadoop	2.0	2016	0 Year(s) 4 Month(s)	
Angular	8	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Expert			
marathi	Proficient			
marwari	Proficient			

Projects

Project Title: American Medical Association(Ruc Database)

Client: American Medical Association Nature of Employment: Full Time

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Mar 2020 - Sep 2020 Role: Programmer Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 8
Skill Used: Angular 8, Java 8, Spring Data JPA, Junit Mocito, Javascript, Spring Boot

Role Description: Full stack developer

Project Details: Ama promoted art and science of medicine. It helps more than 500 physician and medical staff to gather

information about CPT(Current procedural Terminology).

Project Title: Texture Health

Client: Ccc, Integrated Health Partners, Blue Cross Blue Shields

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Feb 2017 - Aug 2019 Role: Programmer Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 10

Skill Used: Angular, Java, Spring, javascript, Jquery, Mongodb, SQL, Git

Project Details: Texture Health, LLC (hereinafter Texture Health, we or us) operates one or more websites (the Website) to provide technology solutions that enable health systems to improve patient outcomes and reduce costs of care.

Project Title: DataBase Migration Tool on Hadoop Platform.

Client: Clairvoyant Biz.pvt.ltd Nature of Employment: Full Time

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Project Location: pune.

Duration: Jan 2016 - May 2016

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 2

Skill Used: BigData Hadoop, Html, Css, Css3, Jsp, Java.

Role Description: Worked as a programmer and web designer.

Project Details: As the name implies Migration tool using hadoop platform,in this we can import any data of database eg. Mysql to Hadoop. Hadoop uses its ecosystem such as Sqoop and Hive to implement data migration. The high scalability

features make hadoop an ideal platform for storing database data.

Languages used: Html,CSS,Jsp,Mysql,Hadoop Framework.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=42a5b7795ee4fb191992ddeb18e5a1de5f5458074c4658190a17420e0e...

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time